An eight-day supply
of food and water, a crossbow...
...season two of
Star Trek: The Original Series...
...on a high-density flash drive.
(Elizabeth:)What if there's a disaster
that destroys all the USB ports?
(Sheldon:)Then there's really
no reason to live, is there?
(Elizabeth:)Can I ask you a question
about your roommate?
(Sheldon:)He's an odd duck, isn't he?
(Elizabeth:)What's his relationship status?
(Sheldon:)Well, there was
a misbegotten adventure...
(Sheldon:)...with a waitress
who lives across the hall.
(Sheldon:)It ended as inexplicably as it began.
(Sheldon:)They had very little in common
except for carnal activity.
(Sheldon:)That's why I acquired
these noise-canceling headphones.
(Sheldon:)If you decide to use them,
please clean the earpieces afterwards...
(Sheldon:)...with the Wet Wipes
you'll find in the bathroom.
(Sheldon:)They're in the drawer
labeled "Wet Wipes."
(Leonard:)-Okay.
-Good.
(Sheldon:)I'll leave you
to your nighttime ablutions.
(Sheldon:)I've e-mailed you
the morning bathroom schedule.
(Sheldon:)You'll also find a laminated copy
in your welcome packet.
(Sheldon:)On the back of
the emergency-escape-route diagram.
(Elizabeth:)How thoughtful.